Subtitles are color-coded by country,
and this setting cannot be changed.
PHYSICAL: ASIA
11. IMPENETRABLE FORTRESS
The fifth quest of Physical: Asia.
Castle conquest.
When the whistle blows,
you will transport a cargo wagon
through the castle gates
to the finish line.
The castle drawbridge
can be lowered by pulling the lever
on top of the castle wall.
So we'll need to get up there.
Are we supposed to climb up the rope?
Yeah, I think so.
The gap at the end of the drawbridge
must be filled with wooden beams
before you can wheel the wagon across.
Those must be the beams.
The castle gates
will need to be struck open.
We've got to strike them open with that.
Upon entering the castle gates,
you must cross the finish line
with the front wheels of the wagon.
Pulling the ropes inside the gates…
and closing the drawbridge shut…
will complete the game.
The country that takes the longest
to conquer the castle
will be eliminated immediately.
…eliminated immediately.
Damn, that sounds tough.
The time limit is
one hour.
If you fail to fully raise the drawbridge
within the time limit,
you will be shortlisted for elimination.
If more than one country is shortlisted,
the ranking will be determined
by the time at which
the front wheels of the wagon
crossed over the finish line.
Okay, I got the hang of it.
The wagon was larger than a van,
and it was fully loaded with sandbags.
We were meant to push
the entire wagon up the sand mound.
I was certain
that no one could beat us at this.
As the shipwreck
transportation match proved,
these kinds of quests
demand teamwork and strategy.
Since those skills are our forte,
we're guaranteed to win.
First place is ours.
Our primary focus
should be hauling the wagon.
Let's try pushing it to gauge the weight.
BAGS + CRATES
WAGON
If it doesn't budge,
we'll jump in and unload the cargo.
The initial plan was
to try hauling the wagon up
without unloading anything.
We figured unloading the cargo
would be time-consuming,
and we didn't have any time to waste.
If the wagon didn't budge,
we'd unload the sandbags.
If it still didn't budge,
we'd unload the crates.
As soon as we begin,
Seung-yeon will run over
and the rest will haul one obstacle each.
One crew will load the sandbags,
another will lay the beams,
and the third will move the wagon.
We divided up the roles.
Just like in
the shipwreck transportation match,
we knew that dividing up the tasks
would be crucial.
I had a clearly defined role,
so my focus was on nailing it
as an essential part of the team.
Republic of Korea!
-Let's go!
The fifth quest.
The castle conquest.
-Think of this as our last shot!
-Once the whistle blows,
-Man, I'm shaking.
-the match will begin.
Stand by.
Ready…
-Damn, this is heavy.
-This is heavy.
I'll help with that. One, two, three.
There we go.
I was given a role too.
I had to climb the rope as fast as I could
and drop the drawbridge.
Of course I was nervous.
But climbing ropes
is something I do all the time.
I can even do it with just my arms,
without using my legs.
Let's give it a push now.
Seung-yeon's climbing up fast!
She's already up there!
I was pumped to see
Seung-yeon climbing so fast.
I looked up after
moving the obstacles aside,
and she was already almost at the top.
That really fired me up.
There's no doubt she's number one in Asia.
Let's go.
Great job, Seung-yeon. Be careful.
When the drawbridge came down,
it felt as if the gates of hope
had opened up to us.
All we had to do now
was just walk right in.
Let's check out how heavy this is, guys.
All right. Come over here, Min-jae.
-Over here.
-Good.
Eun-sil, push from the back with us.
All right.
One, two, three!
Two, three.
That's it! It's moving!
-Let's keep pushing!
-Let's go. Keep pushing.
We didn't expect it to budge at all.
So when it began to move,
we knew we had a chance.
We were able to push it on flat ground,
so I figured the rest would be a breeze.
-One, two.
-Two.
-Seung-yeon, come to the front.
-Okay.
-One, two.
As we moved steadily forward,
I started to believe we could even
push it up the hill without a problem.
-If this works, we're home free!
-One, two!
-One, two.
-That's it.
-One…
-Shit, we're stuck.
-We're stuck.
-One…
-Shit, we're stuck.
-We're stuck.
Are we stuck?
-Let's unload the cargo.
-Yeah, unload it.
-It won't push, right?
-No.
Let's unload for the uphill.
Throw them as close as you can
to the castle.
Okay.
-Are we unloading everything?
-Yeah.
Let's at least get the sandbags off.
No one waited around.
Everyone immediately
rushed onto the wagon to unload.
We all felt the halt at the same time.
Get down now.
Get down, guys.
Loading the crates off the wagon
was our absolute last resort.
We knew how heavy the crates were
from the shipwreck transportation match.
We didn't wanna risk it again.
-All right, let's push now. Come down.
-Okay.
Our plan was to unload just the sandbags
and push the wagon across in one go.
-One, two, three!
Two, three!
One, two.
-One, two.
-Yes, we're moving!
Come on, put some muscle into it.
-We get it up the hill, and we're set.
-One, two.
We started pushing again,
and it began to move up the hill.
It moved, but just barely.
One, two, three.
Shit.
-Two, three.
One.
Push! Two, three!
-One, two, three.
One, two, three!
Push. One, two, three!
-One, two, three.
One, two, three!
Man, it was tough.
There was no traction underfoot
because it was just pure sand.
The wagon wouldn't budge.
It was like pushing against a wall.
Desperation kicked in then.
The weight was still too much.
I realized that the only way
to get the wagon up the hill
was to unload the crates.
One, two, three!
-Block the wheels while I hold it.
-Wedge the bags under.
-Throw them under.
-Okay.
We need to take more weight off the wagon.
Let's unload more weight.
We wedged the sandbags under the wheels
to keep the wagon from rolling back.
After securing the wheels,
we climbed up the wagon
to pull the crates off.
I was anxious because
I dreaded having to unload the crates,
but there was no choice.
All right.
-Watch out.
-Okay.
-All right.
-One, two.
Be careful.
The crates were quite heavy.
Even as I unloaded them,
I was already worrying
about loading them back on.
I felt hopeless,
like it was all over for us.
Watch out, Min-jae. Move.
All I could think was, "We're in trouble."
-Pick up the pace, guys.
-Okay.
Let's all move a bit faster.
-Clear the way.
-Just shove it off.
All right, let's go.
Let's go. We need to hurry.
We're running out of time.
One, two, three!
-Two, three!
-One, two.
-One, two!
-We're almost there!
-Yes!
-One, two!
-Just a bit more!
We're here!
-One, two!
The wagon suddenly felt much heavier
when we reached the top of the hill.
Perhaps it's just human nature
for things to feel harder
when the end is in sight.
We're almost there.
All right!
-Keep pushing!
One, two.
MOUND CLEARED
All right, stop.
The sandbags.
We wasted so much time
getting the wagon up the hill
that we were desperately scrambling.
I was anxious
about the cargo we had emptied.
It all had to be hauled up the hill,
and I knew it would be a long haul.
Okay, carry the sandbags up first.
Get the sandbags.
We'll move the crates together.
Let's speed up. We've lost a lot of time.
Sung-bin, let's move this together.
-Hold it.
-Damn, it's heavy.
It's heavy. One, two, three.
Mind your steps.
Let's set it down first.
Now turn it over.
-The hard part's over after this!
-Just one more crate.
Let's go.
-One, two, three.
Loading the sandbags was manageable,
but having to load all the crates
was daunting.
-One, two, three.
Unloading was the easy part.
Getting them back on was the real deal.
Damn, he can load that thing by himself?
I have to say,
he saved the day.
-One, two, three.
The rest of us were teaming up
two to a crate, using steps and all.
While Min-jae was just
hauling the crates up in one go
and throwing them over.
He proved the power of a Cheonhajangsa.
If we were to keep up the pace,
we'd fill up the wagon in no time.
Seung-yeon, help me carry the ram.
It's too heavy for just us two.
Seung-yeon, grab here.
One, two, three.
One, two, three. Okay.
This is pretty heavy.
Our aim was to move the ram
as close to the gates as possible.
Set it down for a second.
But it was too heavy
for two women to carry.
One, two, three.
It felt really heavy
when we first picked it up.
But Eun-sil is quite strong,
and it was actually manageable together.
-Let's put it down.
-Okay.
Okay.
All right. One, two, three!
Yes! We're good!
Let's smash those gates. Come on.
Let's go. On one, two, three.
Let's do this.
Let's aim for the middle.
Let's do it in one go.
-One, two…
-On three.
On this count!
-Three!
-Go again!
-Again.
Let's aim slightly higher.
Set, go.
-One!
-Two!
-Next count. Focus!
-Three!
One more time.
Even the count-off
felt like a waste of time.
On the count of two. Let's go.
-One!
On this count!
-We're close. Once more!
-Once more.
Come on, we're almost there!
-On two.
-Okay.
-One, two!
-One!
Throw it!
Nice, we're in!
CASTLE GATES CLEARED
Let's go.
Let's push!
Let's go. Come on, Min-jae.
This is the final push, guys.
-One!
-Two!
-Three!
-Push!
-Let's go!
-Go.
We got it!
-Keep going, all the way!
-Let's go all the way!
Wait, watch out!
Wait, we're going to hit the right side!
We're stuck. Back up, back up!
I knew we had messed up.
I'll steer from the front!
-Dong-hyun, get in. I need help.
-Okay.
Push it back a bit.
-Back up a bit!
-Okay!
-One, two, three.
It's not working.
Two, three. It's not working.
Amotti and I tried to steer the wagon,
but it wouldn't even budge.
I was sweating bullets
because getting held up there
could cost us the challenge.
It's moving. Hang on, back up.
-One, two, three!
Once Sung-bin jumped in,
the three of us pulling together
finally got the wagon shifted.
As expected of him.
When it comes to power,
it's nobody but Sung-bin.
-One, two, three!
-One, two!
-All right!
-One, two, three!
-One, two!
-All right!
-One, two, three!
One, two, three!
-Okay, we're good to go.
-Let's go!
All right!
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
Come on, push.
-Let's keep pushing!
-Let's go!
I could see the finish line ahead of us,
and I was dying to cross it.
Let's push from behind.
-One, two, three!
One, two, three!
Two, three!
It's moving. Go!
Don't stop!
-Don't stop. Keep pushing.
-Go!
Come on, we're almost there.
This is our last one today.
The last of our lives.
This is it!
The final stretch on the sand
was the toughest.
We had to push when we were already spent.
This is it!
One, two, three!
Perhaps it was because we were wiped out,
but the wagon refused to move.
We'll push again on the count of three.
All right, one, two, three!
Let's go again.
-One, two, three!
Come on, we've got to push!
One, two!
The wheels got stuck in the sand
and came to a dead stop.
It was a race against time.
I was so anxious that we'd lose.
We were stuck
with the finish line just inches away.
I was losing it.
Amotti, help me move
the sand out of the way.
Get the sand out.
Get the sand out!
Get it out.
That's enough. Let's go.
That should be enough. It'll move now.
Push together, guys. Let's nail it in one!
-One, two, three!
-Three!
-Good.
-Okay, we're moving.
Okay, this is good.
We're almost there. Just keep pushing.
One more push. We're almost done.
We just need to get over the ridge.
This is it now.
-Just one more push.
-Set, go.
-One, two, three!
We've got to push!
-Three!
-Go again.
-One more time, straight ahead.
-Ease back a bit. One, two, three!
-Two!
-Push!
-Straight into another push!
No, this isn't working.
Man, I resented that ridge
right at the end.
-One, two, three!
-Two, three!
-Three!
-We've done it!
-All right!
-Done.
-We've done it!
-All right!
-Done.
FINISH LINE CLEARED
Nice! We're done with the cargo.
We weren't in the clear just yet.
Looking behind us,
there was the drawbridge
that needed to be shut.
Quick, back up. Us three here.
Let's do this.
All that was left
was closing the drawbridge.
We just had to close it shut,
and we were done.
Ready, set, go!
On the first pull,
I couldn't believe how heavy it was.
The drawbridge wouldn't budge,
and I wondered if pulling it shut
would be possible.
We need to back up further.
Back up.
Back up farther, like we talked about.
Back up, back up!
Min-jae, come back farther!
We'd planned out ahead of time
that we'd pull from a distance.
When we pull the drawbridge,
think of it as a tug-of-war.
We'll line up straight
and back up as far as we can.
Three on each side will pull from far back
so the rope stays nearly horizontal.
If we're pulling from too up front,
we wouldn't get real leverage,
so we'd back up as far as possible
and throw our full weight into it.
Min-jae, back up one more step.
Move farther back.
Are we all set? Ready, set, go.
One, two.
It's working. One, two.
-One, two.
-Alternate hands.
-It'll keep getting easier.
-One, two.
One, two.
With every pull, our combined strength
lifted the drawbridge bit by bit.
-One, two!
We kept pulling with
every last bit of strength we had.
-One, two.
One, two.
-Just a bit more!
-One, two.
One, two. One…
That's it!
One… That's it!
Game over.
Good work, guys.
-We got this in the bag.
-We gave our all.
I didn't stop for a second.
Damn, I'm beat.
Great job, Sung-bin!
You didn't let up even once.
I can barely breathe.
It was the toughest match
we've had to do by far.
Hands down.
I think I just burned through
a whole year's worth of energy today.
Of course I was wiped.
But the second I heard
the drawbridge slam shut,
I was ecstatic.
I got chills all over
the moment it closed.
If we lose after all that effort,
I'll accept defeat.
I wouldn't have any regrets
because I left it all out there.
Not everything worked out
perfectly as planned.
Pushing the wagon up the hill
and entering the castle
ended up costing us a lot of time.
Of course there are regrets.
But I still think I did the best I could.
Gather around, guys.
Min-jae, you start us off.
Republic of Korea!
-Let's go!
Physical: Asia.
Team Mongolia, please enter the arena.
Let's go.
What's this?
It looks like a tactical defense setup.
I could see a castle.
It wasn't at all what I expected.
The setup looked like a battlefield
where attacks and conquests take place,
and that intrigued me even more.
It seemed more challenging,
like a different kind of match altogether.
It was very imposing.
What is this? My heart's pounding.
We conquered castles before.
There's no reason
we can't do this, is there?
We Mongolians have long been known
for conquering established castles.
This castle will be no exception,
and we'll conquer it in the shortest time.
The key is getting the wagon
to the bridge as quickly as possible.
-Let's unload all the cargo.
-Yeah, let's get it all off.
You're right. Let's empty all the cargo.
We'll get everything off
while a few of us clear the barricades.
We'll push the empty wagon up there,
and one person will go up
and lower the drawbridge.
-Then we'll get the wagon on the bridge.
-Right.
Let's go with that plan.
Let's show them how it's done.
Stand by.
We're not worried about anything.
Because we know we're stronger
when we work as a team.
Of course, there can only be one winner.
And that's Mongolia.
Ready…
It's important to maintain momentum.
Let's go!
Let's move in sync, guys.
Start pulling right away.
Everyone headed to their designated spots,
and I unloaded the cargo.
I didn't even think about
how much there was to unload.
I only focused on getting it done
as quickly as possible.
I sprinted to the wall
and started climbing up.
Hanging off ropes is basically
what I do for a living,
so I knew this task was mine.
Good job, guys. Good progress.
Given our physical experience,
everything went seamlessly.
Let's take these two.
Leaving them behind
will only cost us time later.
We should get the beams in place now.
Let's give it a go.
I'm sure we can lift them.
Okay, let's push the wagon now.
Get behind it, everyone.
One, two, three!
It's moving.
-One, two!
The wagon felt pretty heavy
as we pushed it through the sand.
It looked light,
but it was actually really heavy.
It required a lot of power.
Come and help us, guys.
Come on, you two. Hurry!
All right, we're coming.
-One, two, three!
-One, two!
Pushing the wagon uphill was tough.
-One, two, three!
It was a lot tougher than expected.
We kept slipping back,
which made it even more difficult.
We pushed with all we had to the top.
-One, two!
That's it, keep pushing!
Great job. It won't roll back.
MOUND CLEARED
Let's put the beams in.
I'm putting it down now.
All right, one, two, three!
One, two, three!
-One, two!
Keep pushing.
We need to stop here
to ram the gates open!
Yeah, you're right.
Over here.
One, two.
Lift.
Let's smash those gates.
This quest was made for us.
-Shouldn't we ram it from here?
-Yeah.
-Hit from afar and get it in one.
-All right!
-Hit it on one side only.
-Let's go.
-One, two, three!
Striking just one side of the gate
focused the impact,
and we were able to snap
the wooden drawbar.
-One, two, three!
CASTLE GATES CLEARED
Let's carry the battering ram inside!
The gates opened quicker than I expected.
It felt natural and easy,
like we'd always smashed the gates
to get home.
Okay, get in the wagon!
One of you, come up with me.
Okay, you and me.
-Here, take it.
-Pass it over.
Grab them and load them quickly.
They need to be in the wagon at the end.
We tried to keep moving
as fast as we could
without stopping
and holding each other up.
We tried to stick closely to our plan
without wasting unnecessary energy.
Hang back, Lkhagva-Ochir.
I'll throw them up,
so pass me the ones that are farther away.
-We're done, we're done.
-Let's go.
Someone has to steer from the front.
All right, steer the wagon.
-Faster, faster!
-Pick up the pace!
-Keep pushing!
-Come on, let's go!
-Go!
-Go, go!
-Go! One, two!
Go, go!
Let's go!
Hey, they mark the time
when the wheels cross the line!
Go!
Let's get the wheels over!
We needed to reach the finish line,
but the sand got in the way.
We got stuck,
and the wagon stopped completely.
It totally threw me off.
I had no clue what was going on.
-One, two, three!
Let's push the wheels!
Come on, push the wheels.
Push the wheels!
One, two, go!
Two people pushed the rear wheels,
while another two pushed the front ones.
And we finally got rolling.
That's it!
-One, two, three!
One, two, three!
Just another meter!
-Two, three!
Come on!
Just a bit more. One, two, three!
-Just a bit more!
-One, two, three!
Okay, we're right on the ridge!
Just a bit more.
-One, two, three!
Come on, move!
-Just a bit more!
-One, two, three!
FINISH LINE CLEARED
-Are we over the line?
-We're over!
Okay, it's time to close the drawbridge.
I think it's been about 15 minutes.
Quick, let's close it.
What are we meant to do?
We have to pull it up.
We need to pull up the drawbridge.
Adiyasuren and Orkhonbayar,
you guys take each side at the back.
Take the rope on your shoulders.
All right, three on each side.
Enkh-Orgil, you're over on that side.
Tie the ropes to the wheels.
Tie them to the wheels.
We tried using the wagon's weight
to pull the ropes.
-One, two, three!
-Pull again. One, two.
-One, two, three.
It's not closing.
All right, again.
The hardest part of the fifth quest
was closing the drawbridge.
I don't know
how much the drawbridge weighed,
but it was unbelievably heavy.
We tried pulling it
with our bodies almost horizontal.
Man, it was tough.
We were totally stumped.
At that point,
we weren't sure it could even close.
We had no idea the drawbridge
would be that heavy.
It refused to even budge.
It's not budging.
We're just moving the wagon.
All we're doing is shifting the wagon.
My mind just went blank in that moment.
We're probably at around
15 or 20 minutes now.
I trusted my team,
but I was panicking inside.
I was terrified we'd be eliminated.
We were out of ideas
and totally sweating it.
The clock was still ticking.
Hey, guys, I have an idea.
Come over here and help me lift the ram.
Help me lift this.
Let's wrap the ropes around it
and pull them down with it.
This is heavy, so it'll work.
Look, Orkhonbayar, listen to me.
Help me lift this.
We'll wrap the ropes around it.
Come on, lift it with me.
-Are you trying to throw it or what?
-No, we'll wrap the ropes and lift it.
-Cut the nonsense. You're wasting time.
-Listen to me.
We can't pull the ropes with this log.
What are you trying to do?
Just trust me.
Everyone, wrap the ropes around this
as many times as you can.
This little log isn't going to
lift the bridge, man.
What are you talking about?
This isn't going to work.
Let's just give it a shot, okay?
We started arguing,
saying the idea wouldn't work.
But like it or not,
we didn't have any other ideas,
so we went along with Enkh-Orgil's plan
and wrapped the ropes around the ram.
To the inside.
The battering ram we used
to smash the gates open was so heavy
that even several of us together
could barely lift it.
I figured if we harnessed the log's weight
as well as our own,
we would have a chance
at hauling the drawbridge up.
Can we get this done in time?
Okay, jump onto it. Hold tight.
-One, two, three!
Great job. Let's pull now!
When we pressed down on the ram,
the bridge that hadn't budged before
finally lifted up a little.
Again! One, two, three!
We immediately sat on it
and started pulling with our hands.
-One, two, three!
-Three!
Hell yeah!
Game over.
Awesome! We did it.
Who came up with such a brilliant idea?
That was badass, Enkh-Orgil.
That was a great idea.
Pulling by hand wasn't going to work.
That was a killer idea.
Awesome job, man.
It was a killer idea indeed.
Solid work, guys.
I'm ecstatic.
And I'm sure the other two teams
won't come up with a trick like ours.
-Warriors!
-Mount up!
Oh man.
-Let's all work together to nail this.
-All right.
-We'll pull our weight.
-Right.
Let's just give it our all,
and we'll be fine.
Team Japan, please enter the arena.
-Let's do this!
-Yeah!
-A rickshaw.
What's this?
-Are we hauling this?
-By unloading it?
There was a wagon
that looked really heavy.
This was going to be
one hell of a challenge.
I wouldn't expect anything less
of Physical: Asia's fifth quest.
There was a massive structure
in front of us.
It was like a huge, castle-like mansion.
I thought, "Why is there a castle?"
I wasn't sure what was going on,
and my head was spinning with questions.
-Six.
-So that's twelve.
My instinct told me right away
that the wagon would be
impossible to move while fully loaded.
Let's unload the sandbags first
and give it a shot.
If that doesn't cut it,
we'll take out 2 crates
to reduce another 100 kg.
We got totally crushed by
Teams Mongolia and Korea
in the shipwreck transportation match,
so this was our shot at payback.
-One, two, three! Go, Japan!
-Go, Japan!
The fifth quest.
The castle conquest.
Stand by.
We have always come back strong
to take the win,
so I was fully confident we'd take down
Teams Mongolia and Korea.
All right, let's do this!
-If you're struggling, just call for help.
-Okay.
-Let's keep talking.
-That's right, keep communicating.
I want a decisive win in this quest
to advance to the final.
Ready…
Since it was impossible
to push the wagon loaded up to the top,
the first task was for our powerhouse,
Katsumi, Itoi, and me
to unload some of the cargo.
For this quest,
it was crucial to handle every step
calmly and quickly.
I kept telling myself to stay calm
and to keep the pace.
With so many things to clear
on the way to the finish line,
it was key to divide up the roles
and keep pushing forward without stopping
while nailing everything along the way.
Should we try pushing the wagon now?
One, two.
No, it's too heavy.
Hold on, I'll join in.
One, two.
No, we have to unload more.
It's not budging.
Despite the three of us pushing,
the wagon didn't even budge.
So we figured we'd need to
unload almost everything.
Anyone who's free,
come and move these closer to the wall.
Let's do it.
Let's throw them forward
to move them partway.
Our team wasn't the most powerful,
so we all needed to pitch in to survive.
We got this.
Instead of one person
hauling a load the whole way,
we used teamwork
to move the cargo in a relay style.
-Can you handle it?
-Yeah.
I was determined not to hold my team back,
so I kept pushing forward to do my part.
Come on.
The progress was quick
with everyone carrying their share.
Good.
This is a solid pace.
We believed we were going at a good pace
and progressing smoothly
without losing too much time.
All right.
Heave! Good work.
-Nonoka, we need to move that pole.
-Okay, let's go.
Kana, there's no way. This is too heavy!
Let's do it together!
-We'll do it together!
-Okay.
Okay, let's lift this.
-One, two!
Look ahead.
This is just the beginning!
-Let's go!
-Yeah!
We got this!
Nice!
As Japanese, we're used to seeing scenes
from the Sengoku period
of gates being rammed open
with brute force.
So breaking open the gates
felt like something we had an edge in.
Let's ram this!
-Huh?
-Let's go again.
-One, two.
-Go again.
-Let's get some momentum going!
-Maybe this isn't it.
-It is.
-Are you sure?
-There's no other gate.
Come on.
-Last shot.
-Let's go.
We rammed the gates together
with everything we had,
but they showed no signs of opening.
All we did was dent the surface.
We even hurled ourselves at the gates,
but nothing worked.
-I don't think this is it.
-We're in trouble.
This has got to be it.
-I'm sure it is.
-This is definitely it.
We've got to trust this is right.
Let's just bring up the wagon first.
All right, fine. Let's do it quickly.
What's up with those gates?
Where do we hit?
The gates were a lot sturdier
than we expected.
We just couldn't
afford to keep wasting time,
so we decided to bring the wagon
up to the gates first.
Let's catch our breath first.
We need to push it up in one shot.
-One, two, push!
-One, two.
Push!
-It's moving!
-Let's go in one shot!
It was light, as expected.
I figured that if we all pushed together,
we could pick up speed.
Push with your arms straight!
Use the momentum to keep going!
It'll get harder from here!
Come on.
-One, two!
We came to a complete stop.
The wagon wasn't moving at all.
You sure are experts at coming up
with these brutal matches.
The hill was so steep
that we stopped just short of the top.
I've been through all sorts of training,
but I'd never had to deal with
that kind of weight before.
One, two.
Hold on.
I was starting to doubt we could win this.
I'll lift this up slightly.
You guys push from the back.
-Here goes. One, two!
-One, two!
-Yes, it's working!
-We're moving!
Come on! We're moving!
We pushed with the front wheels
lifted slightly off the ground,
and that got us moving.
-Yes!
-We're moving!
Use your toes!
-Yes!
-We're moving!
-Don't stop!
-Let's go!
This is the last bit!
Push for victory!
-Yes!
-Push for victory!
Last bit!
Don't stop!
All right, stop here.
-How do we open this?
-Are we meant to push together?
We racked our brains
on how to break open the gates.
That's when our resident strategist,
Katsumi Nakamura said…
How about we just charge at it
with the wagon?
So all of us will push it together.
To be honest,
I really didn't think
it was going to work.
-Let's push!
-Hey, guys.
All of you, come to the back.
-Push from behind?
-Yeah.
Here goes.
-One, two!
Believe in ourselves.
We all put our trust in him.
My heart was in my throat.
-We're through!
-Yeah!
CASTLE GATES CLEARED
It felt like we'd gotten through the gates
quite quickly.
If we kept going like we were,
there was no way we'd lose.
We were nearing the finish line.
All right, here goes.
-I'll handle things up here.
-Okay.
We need to start with the 50 kg ones.
-One, two.
The rule was to enter the castle gates
with all the cargo on board,
so we all worked together
to quickly reload everything on the wagon.
Two, three.
We got this. Let's go!
We're down to just the sandbags now.
Let's load them up.
I'll help.
We got this.
I was sweating buckets.
We were all running on fumes by then.
-Let's go.
Let's do this!
I was already worried about
how heavy the wagon would be
now that all the cargo was loaded back on.
We weren't able to push it earlier
when all the cargo was loaded, after all.
Let's do this!
Build momentum, guys.
-Build momentum! Run!
-Run, run!
The wagon started rolling without a hitch.
We wanted to use the momentum
to go all the way to the finish line.
But it came to a dead stop
as soon as we hit the sand.
It was stuck.
What happened?
We've got to hit the finish line.
-Where's the line?
-There.
Oh, right. Let's try pulling then.
Itoi, you push from the back.
-Should we lift it again?
-Good call.
We're lifting the front.
-One, two!
We're not unloading everything again,
are we?
We've got to do this.
Heave, guys! One, two!
We were racing against the clock
for the rankings,
and we were panicking.
Can you two lift this up?
Just like how you'd do a squat.
-Bend over with your hips back.
-Okay.
-And lean on this?
-Right.
-Oh, here?
-Yeah.
We were told to lift up the front wheels
as if we were lifting a heavy load.
One, two!
We got this!
We can do this. Let's go!
For the win!
One, two!
We put ourselves in rhythm once again.
We pushed forward, step by step,
shouting, "One, two!" as we went.
-All together! One, two!
-One, two!
One, two!
That's it, come on!
-Can we do a swap, Okami?
-Sure.
It was so excruciating and never-ending.
-Come on!
-Let's go!
One, two!
-That's it.
-We got this.
-Yes, yes.
-Come on!
Yes.
Go, go!
One, two!
-We got this!
-We can do it!
Let's finish in the next push!
-Okami, can you kick here?
-One, two!
All right, from here.
Lift it up now, and we're done!
-Final push.
-Last two pushes!
We just need to get it over the line!
One, two!
We can do this!
-All right!
-We've cleared it!
-Let's close the drawbridge!
-Close it!
We were all pumped
when the wheels finally crossed the line.
-Pull the ropes to finish!
-Where are the ropes?
But there was no time to revel in the joy.
The quest wasn't over
until the drawbridge was closed shut.
-Let's do it together, Itoi.
-Here.
-How do we do this?
-Is it this?
We all pull together.
-Pull both sides.
-Use your body weight.
Let's pull!
One, two!
It's lifting!
Come on, come on!
It worked!
All of us pulled the ropes
with everything we had.
And we managed to
get the bridge up halfway.
-Pull, pull!
-We have to pull away.
-Away from here?
We believed we were
far ahead of the other teams.
One, two!
It seemed momentum was on our side.
Come on, close!
Hello, my friend!
The losing team
will be smashing their torsos.
The losing team's torsos
will be shattered.
Come on. Please.
Everyone looks relaxed and happy.
They're walking in smiling.
They've got huge grins on their faces.
Damn, I guess we've got to
keep smiling too.
-Everyone's smiling, Dong-hyun.
-Yeah.
They all look happy.
I wondered who'd won,
as we didn't know our finish times.
Physical: Asia.
The fifth quest, the castle conquest,
has been completed.
Among Teams Japan,
the Republic of Korea, and Mongolia,
only two countries will survive…
while the lowest-ranked country
will be eliminated immediately.
Man, one of us will be going home.
Now, the first country
to advance to the final quest
will be announced.
Physical: Asia.
The first country
advancing to the final quest is…
I can't bear to listen.
I hoped against hope
that we had won first place.
-Should we all hold hands?
-What?
Should we hold hands?
I think we had good teamwork
and did a good job.
We went all out,
so I'm confident we've won this.
I was really happy with how we performed.
So I'm pretty sure we're in first place.
Man, I'm losing it.
Republic of…
Come on.
…Team Republic of Korea.
Holy shit!
We won!
If I'm being honest,
we never doubted the result.
We knew we'd won,
because there was no other possibility
than winning this.
That's how hard we had worked.
The constant shouts of encouragement
and matching our moves to our counts
fired us up more than ever.
I'm so grateful to my teammates
for hauling the cargo
without a single break or complaint.
The fact that all six of us
were in it together as a team
gave me a great boost of motivation.
Our teamwork was truly at 100%
when we closed the drawbridge.
We were perfectly in sync.
Republic of Korea!
-Let's go!
This proves we can win
when we give it our all.
I'm confident about the final quest.
We just have to do what we did this time.
…Team Republic of Korea.
I was shocked when Team Korea
was announced as the winner.
I had a bad feeling
that we were about to get eliminated.
What was their record? Tell us their time.
Team Republic of Korea's finishing time
is 17 minutes and 53 seconds.
-No way.
-That's so fast.
Seventeen minutes? That's insane.
-They closed the bridge in 17 minutes?
-Yeah.
When I heard
that they finished in 17 minutes,
I was at an absolute loss for words.
Pulling up the drawbridge
in 17 minutes is insanely fast.
I don't understand how they managed that.
They're shocked.
We were insanely fast, guys.
We must've been really fast
if they're that shocked.
Oh boy, we made the final.
Now, the second country
to advance to the final quest
will be announced.
My heart's pounding.
I could feel my pulse quickening.
I was so scared that we'd get eliminated.
The last country
advancing to the final quest is…
I was desperately hoping
that Team Japan would be called out.
Mongolia.
Come on, come on.
The last country
advancing to the final quest is…
Subtitle translation by: Jee Butcher